callcentric.com 2006-06-25

# Callcentric - Privacy Policy

| **PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT**  
---  

Callcentric respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites. This privacy statement provides notice of our information collection practices and of the ways in which your information may be used.  

**Collection / Use of Information:**

Callcentric collects personally identifiable information for the purposes of registering, provisioning, troubleshooting, billing, fraud detection, informing customers of new Callcentric products and services, and general operations of the Callcentric website and services.

Callcentric will not disclose, share, transfer, sell or rent personally identifiable information to any third party or partners without the consent of the customer except as required by subpoena, search warrant or other legal process or in the case where failure to disclose information will lead to imminent harm to the customer or others. This includes information derived from registration, subscription, billing information, and use of the Callcentric service.

Callcentric will not display or make publicly available, whether through online directories, customer lists or otherwise, the personally identifiable information collected. The exception to this is a listing within the Callcentric Directory which is available to all Callcentric customers. Customers may remove themselves from the Callcentric Directory by either selecting to not be included when signing up for the Callcentric service, or by logging into their account and removing themselves from the Callcentric Directory under the Preferences section at any time.

Callcentric will not read, listen to or disclose to any third parties private e-mail, conversations, or other communications that are transmitted using Callcentric services except as required to ensure proper operation of services or as otherwise authorized by law.   

**Security:**

When Callcentric asks users to enter sensitive information, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our registration form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just "surfing".

Callcentric may use all customer identifiable information to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful or fraudulent activity or activities that threaten the integrity of the Callcentric service, our network integrity, or otherwise violate the Callcentric Terms and Conditions.   

**Other:**

This Callcentric site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may update it at any time by logging into your account. If you no longer desire our service you may request to cancel your Callcentric account by 

[_opening a trouble ticket_](https://my.callcentric.com/customer.php?f=opentt).   

**SPAM / SPIT Policy:**

Callcentric has zero tolerance for Spam and Spam over Internet Telephony (SPIT). Spam and SPIT complaints will be dealt with seriously and may result in cancellation of your Callcentric account.   

**Children's Privacy Policy:**

Callcentric does not provide products or services for use or purchase by children. Callcentric does not knowingly solicit or collect customer identifiable information from children or teenagers under the age of eighteen. If you believe that a minor has disclosed personally identifiable information to Callcentric, please 

[_contact us_](http://www.callcentric.com/contact/) so that the information can be removed.  
  
\--Updated Dec 29, 2005
